Hamid Safdari

Developer/Editor

Java Script | React | Node js | MongoDB |

About Me

As a developer, I am driven by the desire to create innovative solutions that make a difference in people's lives. I believe that technology has the power to transform the world, and I want to be a part of that transformation.

Every new code I make is due to my passion for programming, and this passion makes the challenges and difficulties on my way easy. So, I love experiencing new challenges and always try to push myself to face them. With this approach, I always learn new things and programming never becomes monotonous for me. If your mindset is similar to mine, I would be happy to walk the path together and gain new experiences.

Highlights Of Qualifications

- Talented Developer with extensive experience in JavaScript, Python and PHP; Good knowledge of SQL and NoSQL Databases
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills
- Strong organizational and problem-solving skills with great attention to detail
- Proven ability to learn quickly; willing to learn new technologies and skills

EXPERIENCES

Front-end Developer

12/2023 - 12/2024 (1 year)

Charter118 🖸

- Collaborated with other 3 team members to produce a web app which users can reserve flight tickets, hotel reservation and tour packages
- designed and developed a full feature panel for admin and users

Full-stack Developer

2020 - 2023 (3 years)

Freelance

- Collaborated lots of projects in front and back-end
- Developed many projects from scratch like "RealEstate", "Jobify" and etc.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree — *Computer Engineering* 2018 - 2023

Bahar Institute of Higher Education

Phone:

0939-495-7726

E-Mail:

i.hamidsafdari@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://hamidsafdari.onrender.com/

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/hamid-safdari-08895a290

Github:

https://github.com/HamidSafdari7

Languages:

Persian

Mother tongue

English

Advanced and fluent in all skills (Speaking - Listening - Reading - Writing)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web technologies

- HTML
- CSS
- React js
- Node Js
- Express Js
- Redux
- Tailwind Css
- Github

Databases

- MongoDB
- MySql

Editing technologies

- Photoshop
- Adobe premier
- Adobe aftereffects

WEB PROJECTS

#1 — My Portfolio

hamidsafdari.onrender.com

Technologies used:

HTML - CSS - Java Script - Bootstrap - Git

#2 — Jobify

<u>hs7-jobify.onrender.com</u> <u>View Src Code</u>

Technologies used:

Front: HTML - CSS - Java Script - React - Material UI - UseReducer - UseContext - Styled Component

Back: Node Js - Express Js **DataBase**: MongoDB

#3 — RealEstate

hs7-realestate.iran.liara.run View Src Code

Technologies used:

Front: HTML - CSS - Java Script - Jquery -

Bootstrap

Back: PHP - Laravel 10

DataBase: MYSQL

#4 — Shopify

shopify-five-blond.vercel.app View Src Code

Technologies used:

Front: HTML - CSS - Java Script - React - Tailwind Css -

Redux -

Back: Node Js - Express Js **DataBase**: MongoDB

#5 — Landing Page

<u>hs7-landingpage.vercel.app</u> <u>View Src Code</u>

Technologies used:

Front: HTML - CSS - Java Script - React - Tailwind Css -

Redux -

#6 — Charter 118

charter118.ir

Technologies used:

Front: React

Back: Laravel - PHP **DataBase**: MYSQL

#7 — PixelBazi

pixelbazi.vercel.app/ View Src Code

Technologies used:

Front: HTML - CSS - Java Script - React - Tailwind Css -

Redux -